<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

<!-- Butcher (Hunter-merchant in the Garbage) -->
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_0">
		<text>Cosy place you have here.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_1">
		<text>Damn right it is! Welcome to the Train Hangar, repurposed by yours truly into a humble hunting lodge. It's a safe place to unwind... for the most part.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_2">
		<text>Tell me more about this lodge of yours.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_3">
		<text>Eh, simply put, this place is for hunters. Whether they're professional or amateur doesn't matter. I reward those who take on hunting jobs for me, I pay well for any mutant trophies you might turn in, and I'll sell you food and hunting equipment real cheap - unlike some other traders around here, the desire to share my passion with others comes first. Never cared much for money grubbers anyways.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_4">
		<text>Are there any other hunters around here, or just you?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_5">
		<text>Hunters from Rostok and Dark Valley tend to stop by here, though it's not always easy getting them to get along.\n \nBesides that, I had a few mates here with me. We were all hunting partners in the outside world, you know? Gonta, Trapper, Fox...all good people. We all got together down here to have a proper funeral for Fox, but sadly the other two couldn't stay - by the sounds of it, the stalkers up north really need them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hunter_trader_meet_6">
		<text>Maybe I'll go pay them a visit sometime.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="about_baraholka_hunter_trader_0">
		<text>Why don't the traders and guards at the flea market live in the hangar? It seems a lot safer, and more habitable.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="about_baraholka_hunter_trader_1">
		<text>You know what I think? I think Duty's high command are secretly paying them to sit there - sort of like lookouts to spy on the goings-on between Rostok and Dark Valley. In any case, those traders don't really have the hunting spirit - for them, it's all "hoard, hoard, hoard"! So really, it's just as well those magpies haven't moved in.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_ask">
		<text>Hey, you've probably hunted loads of mutants in your time. Do you have any stories about them?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_1">
		<text>Ooh, I've got a good one. A few years ago, I took jobs with Duty, helping them clear out mutant lairs.\n \nSo, we're in the Wild Territory, having just cleared the place of Bloodsuckers, Poltergeists, Snorks - that horrible place was thick with them back then. Luckily for Duty, I was skilled enough to ensure we'd only encounter small groups at a time, picking the monsters off one by one.\n \nAnyways, although I did good work, they stubbornly insisted we had to continue until nightfall, then set up camp so we could immediately continue cleaning the next day. "General's orders," they said. Hmph. We were quite far in that area - far off the well-worn path that most stalkers take, but they didn't seem to mind. So we found some ruins of a derelict construction site and set ourselves up there, after climbing the staircase right up to the unfinished top floor.\n \nHours passed, and then I spotted it. A lone tushkano on the ground way below us. Nothing more than a mutated rodent that runs on two legs. It's no bigger than your foot. So, it sniffs the air and then suddenly whips its head in our direction and lets out this blood-curdling shriek.\n \nHundreds upon thousands of the damn gremlins started crawling out of pipes, holes in the earth, other ruins - and began stampeding straight for us.\n \nYou couldn't even see the floor anymore. The Duty troops fought bravely, but they were quickly overwhelmed, forced down to the ground through sheer weight of numbers before having their throats torn out.\n \nI quickly scrambled up the pillar I had been resting on only a moment ago. I started throwing down grenades, blasting with buckshot...even using my knife when a few of the buggers tried to climb or jump up to where I was.\n \nIt was hours of endless shrieking, the stench of blood and death. When dawn broke I was shivering, my coat scratched to hell and my skin crisscrossed with various bite and claw marks.\n \nWhen the little bastards finally got bored and went for an afternoon nap, that's when I came down. I searched for my Duty comrades, but there weren't even bones left behind.\n \nI walked back to Rostok, broken as hell, cursing the lives that were lost that day. I hunt for sport. Duty hunts for the gates of hell itself. Well, they can find their way there themselves. I'm not going with them next time.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_2">
		<text>Oh boy. Let's talk about dogs. I'm sure you've seen a few packs of strays running around the Zone by now. Even the rookies in Cordon have.\n \nGet rid of any thoughts that these are household pets, or that they can be rehabilitated, or tamed. The Zone has touched all these beasts. You ever seen Zone dogs up close? They're blind, with eyes that have withered away generations ago.\n \nFast creatures, too. Their bite isn't the worst injury someone can get in the Zone, but it's enough to slow you down and, if there's a pack nearby, that's enough to end you.\n \nTo top it all off, their sense of smell is even keener than a greyhound's.\n \nYou asked for a story, but I'm not sure what to tell you. I've seen hundreds of rookies and even some experienced stalkers underestimate these creatures and get ripped apart as a result.\n \nEven Military Stalkers get unlucky. Even the best armour merely means these dogs will try to bleed you out rather than tear you up.\n \nMostly though, they prefer to stick to Fleshes, so as long as there's enough wild food around in proportion to the dog population, you should be alright. In some cases, packs would even let me pass unscathed if I just kept a little quiet as I went through. Of course, it's not something I'd try unless there's an anomaly field between you and those canines, the consequences of them getting a little hungry and suddenly changing their minds are...unsettling to witness, at best.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_3">
		<text>Now, every rookie and their grandmother has heard of the dogs that stalk around the Zone. But have you seen a pseudodog yet?\n \nWhile the Zone's 'normal' dogs descend from the generations of strays that made their home in Chernobyl after the accident, pseudodogs instead descend from wolves. Some people say there's some bear or even human DNA mixed in as well, but I have my doubts.\n \nEither way, instead of flabby puppies getting a mean streak put into them, this is just a case of mean bastards getting meaner. Many stalkers either die or get gravely injured in their first encounter with one since they assume it's just another, slightly flat-faced, dog.\n \nIn truth, pseudodogs are smarter, faster and stronger. Some of them can create illusory copies of themselves. Others can psychically compel a stalker to lower his weapon seconds before the kill.\n \nUnlike regular Zone dogs, I've heard legends of stalkers taming these beasts, but I've never seen it with my own eyes. They say the Swamp Doctor has one, but I don't remember any dog around when he healed me all those years ago. Then again, the rumours are relatively recent. Maybe I should track the old guy down and visit him some time? </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_4">
		<text>Let me tell you about the snorks.They're so-called thanks to their masks and the hellish sounds they make through them.\n \nEugh. All those disgusting slurps and grunts.\n \nAnyways, it's a commonly held belief that they're the remains of the first military expeditions into the Zone. We first started seeing them around 2007, when an army guy got attacked by one while waiting for his transport. Back then, we called them "Recruits", not Snorks.\n \nDon't let their grey, decomposing bodies fool you - their muscles are lean and powerful, and they're able to leap great distances through the air to reach their prey. Just one of them is bad enough, but an entire group of Snorks means you may as well save yourself some pain and off yourself right there if you got caught unprepared. Fortunately, they're usually only found in large numbers underground. Well, usually.\n \n The greatest mystery is how they breed - how their numbers stay the way they are despite hunters trying to cull them for years. A passing scientist told me they might be moulages, rather than the remains of real people, but I don't know what that means. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_5">
		<text>Argh. Zombies, zombies, zombies. Have you ever seen a zombie? A real one - not some brain-hungry corpse from TV or a videogame.\n \nWe have a few wandering around the Zone here. Poor guys - most of them are former stalkers who got dragged into a psy-anomaly or trapped near one of the DUGA emitters for too long.\n \nThe truly unfortunate come by this fate when they can't get to cover in time during an emission - maybe you laugh now, but it's no joke.\n \nThey're some of the worst hunting experiences in my life. Not because they're particularly challenging - while they retain the ability to use weapons and tools, they're also slow, oblivious and not all that fast. They're the worst because you can still see a shell of a man buried in them somewhere.\n \n"Soldier, soldier! Help me, I'm over here!"\n \n"Just one more artefact, just one more... and maybe I can see my daughter again."\n \nThose are the kind of things I keep hearing from them, and it keeps me up at night. Not that I'm soft, it just seems like one of the worst ways to die in the Zone, you know?\n \nSome of the Zombies look a lot older, and closer to what you'd see in the films. They have no clothes except rags, no tools except their fingernails. How do they reach that point? Maybe they're the earliest surviving zombified stalkers. Perhaps they're the remains of Pripyat's original inhabitants. Or, as one scientist said, they're just moulages. What is a moulage, you ask? Hell if I know.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_6">
		<text>Let me think for a moment.\n \nHave you ever come across a Bloodsucker? They're tall, predatory humanoids with a mess of tentacles where their mouths should be. I've hunted many in my time.\n \nThey're like vampires - when they're hunting, they cloak themselves so that you cannot see them coming, even in broad daylight. The only way to detect one before its too late is through its ravenous breathing. Once they get close enough, they'll wrap their arms around you, firmly attach their warm, moist tentacles to your bare skin, and suck you dry.\n \nDon't get any ideas - their bodies are rough, often necrotic, and typically they only stop feeding when you're dead. And, unlike what their name suggests, they aren't satisfied with just your blood.\n \nTheir tentacles are drenched in a caustic saliva that prevents your blood from coagulating. In large quantities, this saliva can even cause your organs to liquefy themselves. Bloodsuckers - when given half a chance, leave their prey a dry, empty husk, thin enough to be tossed around by the wind.\n \nAs if that isn't bad enough, they sometimes hunt in groups, too. In these cases, they'll engage in psychological warfare, encircling their prey and hiding their real numbers to overwhelm you while they take turns snacking on your juicy flesh. I've seen Bloodsuckers drive their prey to madness, and even suicide, through this.\n \nThe best way to deal with them is to stay calm, camp somewhere that forces them along a predictable path and punish them for daring to approach you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_7">
		<text>Burers. Christ, you can bet your backside I haven't forgotten about Burers. They love dwelling in dark, empty places - especially laboratories or old factory complexes.\n \nI was wandering around in the Meadow back when I was a much younger lad, with two burly stalkers. One of them - Zest - was dressed head to toe in the best armour money could buy at the time. The other guy, Shawl, stuck to a simple overcoat over a SEVA suit.\n \nWe were trying to track down a potential snork lair, only for Shawl to stop and ask, "What's that? Do you hear that?"\n \nHe had good ears. It was a very faint sound, but you could barely make out the noise of an infant in tears.\n \nNow, even then, none of us were heartless bastards, so off we went to try to find the child. A lot of stalkers think it's only men who get into the Zone, but once in a blue moon I'll meet a woman going around, doing stalker things like anyone else - that said, full-body armour doesn't let you keep a feminine appearance, and everyone uses a false name, but I digress.\n \nThe point is that children do sometimes happen here. But, as is the nature of the Zone, it's extremely rare and doesn't tend to end happily - the few stalkers who find someone to start a family with usually have enough sense to leave the Zone before getting it on - like Nimble and his wife, although I hear Nimble is back now - but not everyone who survives here has common sense, and others simply have their circumstances forced on them.\n \nAnyways, for those who start their whole family right in the Zone, all it takes is one stroke of bad luck to leave the babe an orphan. A second stroke and it becomes Bloodsucker food.\n \nSo, we had to find the child before anything else did.\n \nWe get to the factory complex near the Meadow, and what do we find? A black sack in the corner. "So!" we think, "That's where the sobbing was coming from".\n \nZest nods to us then steps forward. He goes to retrieve the sack, but the damn thing turns itself around, and we see it wasn't a sack at all. It was a filthy, black overcoat. And the thing wearing it was no damn baby.\n \nIt kept weeping, making that sick, gurgling baby sound, then raised its hands and let out a roar that almost split my skull. I could barely stand. Everything suddenly felt so heavy. My coat felt like a sheet of tiles, my gun felt like a cinderblock. An invisible force tore it out of my hands and threw it into the dark of the factory.\n \nZest had it worse. He started squishing, crumpling like a goddamn tin can underneath an invisible boot. He began screaming, his armour just got heavier, tighter, until... I don't even want to say what it looked like. There was no saving him after that.\n \nShawl was struggling, just like I was, but at least he was still alive.\n \nI don't want to relive the whole ordeal to the end, but I can share a few things we learned about Burers from that encounter. Firstly, they don't like being flashed by sudden, bright lights. Secondly, they use the weight of your gear against you - their natural telekinesis becomes a special bitch when Newton gets involved. Thirdly, it takes effort for them to do this. When they tire out, when their hold falters, that's when you spring into action and gut them with your blade. </text> 
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_8">
		<text>Yeah, let me tell you a story about Controllers - also known as Illusionists, among some stalkers.\n \nI was working under Sakharov at the time. Well, not directly. I was working for his assistant, Professor Kruglov. He specialized in mutant studies, and I was interested to hear what kind of things he'd have to say to someone like me.\n \nAs it turned out, he had a whole team of assistants out in the Darkscape, only they hadn't managed to contact him in over a week, and he was starting to get suspicious. So he sent me to go track them down, make sure they're still breathing.\n \nWell, they were still breathing.\n \nThey were fooling around in some bridge-tunnel, walking about in the nude. I thought maybe they got stuck up real bad by some bandits. Or maybe that these young nerds were feeling a little - eheh - experimental.\n \nBut no, the real reason was much worse, but I didn't know better back then .\n \nThere were around five of these eggheads. I kept myself hidden, to discern what the hell was going on.\n \nWell, one of them suddenly tore their own throat out. The other smacked his head against the wall until it cracked like a nut. The third guy - who was supposed to be some sort of guard - he just... gun in his mouth and...\n \nYeah.\n \nThe last two just stood there as the Controller finally stepped out of the shadows of his cavernous lair - I later found records, left by this confused team, that paint a gruesome picture, where these bright young men slowly started losing their minds, getting headaches, sweating profusely. Their senses were toyed with until they had no sense left, just rambling around gormlessly, exposed to the elements. This is why our surviving couple just stood there as the damn monster broke their arms, then their legs - well, they weren't standing after that. They didn't even scream. They just lay there. The Illusionist went back to start sinking his teeth into their dead friends, and they didn't even care, they only...\n \nMm. No.\n \n I tried to save them, but I couldn't get close enough to the Controller with my shotgun without this sweet voice in my ear, urging me to drop my weapon and quietly surrender myself. I wanted to listen. I craved to obey. I had to back off and take cover before I wound up like those damn scientists.\n \nIn the end, I just tossed in a grenade - the Controller may be a master of telepathic manipulation and a terrifying opponent when his attention is on you, but they're too slow to dodge even the most telegraphed pineapple throw.\n \nBetter yet, the worst of their powers can't happen if they can't see you. Grenades don't need line of sight.\n \nAnd that's all you really need to know to kill a Controller. This was all before psy-block, or any meaningful psychic defences had been manufactured.\n \Nowadays, you have more ways to defend yourself from them, but even so, they are no joke. They can slowly erode your will over days, or boil your brain out in a second, depending on whether they want you to serve them or whether they want to eat you. And, as the story with the eggheads demonstrate, the categories sometimes mix. So, do you have any vodka? I could sure do with some right about now. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_9">
		<text>Well, I don't really have a story this time, but something I often heard around my campfires for a while were stalkers complaining endlessly about cats. I don't blame them. These creatures used to be rare - almost unheard of, with only inveterate mutant hunters like Duty or yours truly encountering them with any regularity.\n \nBack in the day, they were just mutated cats. Sure, they were still about the size of a lynx and had grossly large thyroids, but they were docile enough compared to most things in the Zone. Once upon a time, they'd do all they could to stay away from humans.\n \nOh, how things change. Some evil spirit seems to have gotten into them - sometime after 2012 they became vicious, bold. They can even be deadlier than pseudodogs! The only consolation is that cats tend to come in smaller groups.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_10">
		<text>A lot of stalkers believe in all kinds of paranormal nonsense and superstition, so it should be no surprise that one of the Zone's stranger mutants is known as the Poltergeist. What else would you call a translucent orb of light and energy that throws objects at you and generally gets up to mischief?\n \nIt doesn't matter what you believe in - deities, your leaders, your own energy, aliens, whatever. Poltergeists are very real. Maybe you laugh now, but it's best to be aware - not all the stories about them are true. Physical attacks like bullets will kill them quite readily, although you'll battle to hit them with a blade. But, for the love of God, don't try to throw grenades at them. They're masters of telekinesis, and they're quick bastards too - it's just a bad idea.  Folklore that says you can kill them with salt, prayer or exorcisms are, unfortunately, misleading, and more than a few hunters have died trying to prove otherwise.\n \nThe real trick to taking these buggers out is through motion. The slower you move, the calmer your actions, the less likely it is to see you. In this way, it's incredibly easy to avoid a poltergeist if there's nothing else around.\n \nOtherwise, they'll pelt you with objects. Or maybe incinerate you by conjuring burner anomalies out of thin air. Luckily, you can tell what they're likely to do by the colour they glow. Bluish poltergeists are telekinetic, orange ones tend to be pyrokinetic. I've occasionally come across dark ones... those are alright as long as you don't let them touch you. They're fatal otherwise.\n \nBut, whatever you do, keep a firm hold on your gear. The last thing you want is to have your knife yanked out of your hands by an invisible force, only to be slowly bled to death with it. Once they have something like that, all it takes is a little cut here, another one there, until blood starts draining out of you like a colander.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_11">
		<text>I remember, back in my rookie days, there'd be hushed talks of tall, slender abominations that skulk through the night. These creatures made for popular campfire stories, and are called Fractures - humanoid creatures with hypertrophic arms and necks. They possess one abnormal, bucketed hand that can strike with enough force to break a person's chest. Their second hand is, thankfully, about as normal as any other human's. I've heard a lot of stories about Fractures that claim they'll try to sneak up on stalkers and ask for all kinds of nonsense, from highly specific cans of food to imported toothpaste.\n \nAccording to those myths, if you're unlucky enough not to have what it asks of you, then prepare to fight for your life. If you do have what it wants, then don't rush to hand it over; throw it on the ground away from you, move away from it quietly on all fours, and the Fracture won't harm you.\n \nWell, that's what the stories say, at least. Some stalkers actually believe them, and even leave provisions in places where Fractures have been seen, in vain hopes to drive them off. In my experience, the creatures don't ask for anything and want nothing more than to eat your flesh.\n \nThe parts of the stories about them sneaking up on stalkers are real, however. You never know when a Fracture could be skulking around, so it's always best to keep your eyes open. Still, they're not too difficult to deal with, but only as long as you do not underestimate the reach and power of their hypertrophied hand. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_12">
		<text>Let me tell you about one of the most physically powerful mutants the Zone has to offer: the pseudogiant. Most of them aren't much taller than a man but are many times wider. They can exert colossal force through their powerful limbs - I've seen them crush entire groups of stalkers, soldiers and mercs on their own. It's this ability that earned them their name.\n \nMost stalkers never encounter one - these creatures, despite their fearsome appearance, often prefer to keep to themselves. Pseudogiants like vast caverns, tunnels and enclosed areas, typically acting fiercely protective over them. So, even the rare stalker who does see one rarely lives to talk about it afterwards. But, of course, I've seen one. And I've clearly lived to tell about it.\n \nIt brings me no peace to think that they all come from labs. The monsters all look like someone took the bodies of several men - who knows, maybe women and children too - and melted them together. Aside from their two powerful, grotesque limbs, they often have a bunch of vestigial ones sticking out all over the place. And if you see the vestigial limbs up close, you'll know what I'm talking about.\n \nI think pseudogiants are the result of an experiment done by sick freaks, and the sooner they all get put out of their misery, the better. I can't imagine anyone wanting to live the way they do.\n \nSpeaking of putting them out of their misery - it's always best to bring explosives. Sometimes you're lucky, and the Pseudogiant is wandering the surface, in which case you can leisurely pick at it from a distance. Although this will likely use up most of your shots, it certainly is safer compared to the usual method.\n \nBut in its natural habitat - which doesn't include wide, open vistas - you won't have that luxury. Without explosives, you'll find its skin is too thick. At close-to-medium distances, it'll make its way to you and flatten you into a pancake long before you would've landed a lethal shot. In those cases, it's best just to run, live and prepare to come back another day.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_13">
		<text>Hmmm... I reckon I could share some of my knowledge on chimeras. A nocturnal predator, this creature is easily one of the Zone's best hunters. How so? With four legs and two heads, it is almost impossible to surprise, and difficult to outrun. It is a master of ambush,  startling stalkers by pouncing them from scores of meters away and inducing fear with its stunning roar.  While it might not be as robust nor as brutally powerful as a pseudogiant, it's quicker, smarter and utterly relentless, with claws and fangs that can shred through the most robust protection.\n \nThis knowledge wasn't easily won, however.\n \nAfter all, that's how my mate Fox died. He was out hunting with his best friend,  Trapper - when a Chimera caught them unawares. The harsh twist is that they were actively tracking that beast, and it still got the better of them. Even Gonta lost a friend or two to such accidents, although I hear it's because one of his mates turned out to be a coward.\n \nThey really are such vicious predators. It's best not to go out at night in the north of the Zone because of them, and if you do ever take it upon yourself to hunt one, keep your eyes and ears open, and make sure you keep your friends' asses covered.\n \nHm, what else can I tell you? Ah! As quick as these beasts are, they turn a lot slower than we do. They don't like spaces with lots of corners, but a deft hunter with a shotgun or grenades does. Another method is to keep an anomaly - preferably a burner, electro or whirligig - between yourself and the beast. If you're dealing with an arrogant specimen, it'll try to leap right through the anomaly to get to you. This won't always kill the beast, but it'll go a long way to giving you the edge you need.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_14">
		<text>I'm sure you've seen plenty of boars and fleshes around here. They're one of the more readily consumed mutants around these parts, as most of the stalkers here are much more comfortable eating mutated bacon as opposed to mutated dog. Of course, not everyone can afford to be so picky with what they put in their mouths.\n \nWhen it comes to hunting these creatures, there's a specific trick to it. Fleshes tend to be cowardly, so it's tricky to get close without trapping it first. For this, it's best to step softly and then unload with a shotgun once you're sure you can get most of the pellets where they need to go. One or two clean shots should do it. When the rest of the herd scatters, don't chase them into anomalies, as that wastes the meat.\n \nFor boars... well that's another story. Boars have thick bones protecting their teeny, tiny brains, and unlike the Flesh, the Zone's mutations have made them hyper-aggressive. Once they see you, they'll charge. I've seen so many stalkers foolishly try to gun one down once it starts charging, thinking they'd kill it before it reached them. Nope, nope, nope. Every last one of those fools died painfully, their entrails torn out by savage tusks.\n \n With boars, you need to play the matador. The wild pigs can't exactly turn on a dime, so use corners and clever footwork to sidestep it. From there, you can either shoot it in the side, or you can grab an axe and hack at it. If you're on a budget, I recommend using an axe and making it quick.\n \n I wouldn't overdo it, however. We aren't the only ones who eat these creatures, and overhunting them inevitably leads to far deadlier mutants raiding stalker camps for new sources of sustenance. I mean, knock yourself out if you wish to hunt them. Just know when to stop. </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_15">
		<text>Yeah, let me show you what I've jotted down about Karliks. This rare mutant chiefly resides in underground complexes, particularly the ones which were used for human experimentation before the Zone's birth. Presumably, Karliks were the outcome of such tests. While they do share remarkably similar physical properties with Burers, they don't seem to be able to use telekineses. Instead, the malicious buggers just run up to you and strike with their bare hands. There's a method to that madness, however, as they possess a highly potent psy-aura that can really scramble your brain if you let them stay too close.\n \nOverall, you don't need to worry about them too much as they're not that dangerous if you're fully awake. Just don't slow yourself down with the hysterical laughter you might have when you see Karliks run around on their little legs. Yes, it's happened before...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hunter_gar_trader_life_end">
		<text>I think you should go out and make your own story for a while. I'm done for the moment.</text>
	</string>

<!-- Daytime trader at the flea market -->
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_0">
		<text>What kind of place is this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_1">
		<text>This, fellow stalker, is the flea market. Lots of diggers and small-time traders pawn off old wares as they pass through here. In truth, most of it is pretty garbage, but on special nights we get some real gems coming through, so we make do. So, do you have anything you want to sell?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_2">
		<text>What are your experiences with the other stalkers around here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="baraholka_trader_talking_3">
		<text>What kind of question is that? This is the Garbage. All sorts of people come through these parts. Some are stalkers who want to be traders. Some of them even have some pretty nice stuff to sell. Others are bandits, mercs, even military. Sometimes we get along, sometimes there's a fight. That's why we have guards around.\n \nOthers are Duty. Now, don't get me wrong, Duty soldiers tend to be upright guys individually, but get enough of them into a group, and I swear they become more fanatical than even the Monolith.\n \nOverall, we have mixed, colourful experiences with the different groups around here. As long as they don't disrupt the little market we have here though, we'll get along just fine.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night_0">
		<text>Hey, do you have information on stashes?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night_1">
		<text>Sure do. I'll part with one for six thousand.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night1_0">
		<text>Here. %c[d_orange][6000 RU]</text>
	</string>
	<string id="information_about_stash_barah_night1_1">
		<text>Pleasure doin' business. There ya go.</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
