<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<!--===========================================================
<
< QUEST ITEMS TEXT  STRINGS
<	CoC 1.4.07 - DoctorX Questlines 1.6
<
<	Modified by: DoctorX
<	Last revised: October 06, 2016
<
<===========================================================-->


<string_table>

	<!-- DRX Storyline Documents Quest Item -->
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_name">
		<text>Documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_1_desc">
		<text>Heavily encrypted documents. Most of it is beyond one's ability to crack with what's available, although the introductory page looks like it might be possible. But of course, doing that would be beyond one's paygrade... the job is merely to hand these notes in, not to play around at decoding them.\n \n"Jxu Pedu ev Qbyudqjyed - Jxu Hebu ev Ucyiiyedi yd Ckjqdj Hufhetksjyed\nro Fhevuiieh Q.R. Ijhkwqjiao\n \nQrijhqsj\nQi tucedijhqjut ro Fhevuiieh Xuhcqdd, yj yi ademd jxqj ucyiiyedi sqd fhetksu qhjuvqsji qdt qdecqbyui, mxybu Fhevuiieh Iqaxqhel xqi tucedijhqjut jxqj ucyiiyedi sqd pecryvo bylydw ruydwi. Rkj mxqj qhu jxu uvvusji ev ucyiiyedi ed xkcqd hucqydi?\n \nHuikbji muhu erjqydut ro buqlydw jxu sehfiui ev ijqbauhi sqwut yd efud qyh tkhydw ucyiiyedi. Qvjuh ckbjyfbu juiji, jxu unfuhycudji muhu hufuqjut myjx jxu retyui ev xkcqdeyt ckjqdji iksx qi jxu vqrbut idehai qdt rbeetiksauhi.\n \nMxqj mu vekdt mqi jxqj qd ucyiiyed, mxud secydw ydje sedjqsj myjx q iaubujqb sehfiu, xqi q sxqdsu je shuqju q "cekbqwu" - q bylydw sqij ev vbuix cqtu vhec qdecqbeki fxudecudq, mxysx jxud huqdycqjui jxu reto. Cekbqwui sqd jqau jxu vehc ev idehai, rbeetiksauhi, pecryvyut xkcqdi qi mubb qi iuucydwbo dehcqb xkcqdi, qdt yd qbb sqiui sqd ru tyijydwkyixut vhec jxuyh jhkbo bylydw sekdjuhfqhji ro jxuyh tuqjxbo whuo fqbbeh. Cekbqwui mxe ceij huiucrbut dehcqb xkcqdi unxyryjut jxu qrybyjo je secckdysqju rkj hugkyhut iutqjyed qi jxuo ydlqhyqrbo tyifbqout unjhucu fqhqdeyq, tubkiyedi, eh q tuiyhu je uisqfu ydje jxu kdademd.\n \nSedsbkiyed: q fejudjyqb unfbqdqjyed veh hufhetksjyed qcedw jxu kdyiun ideha secckdyjyui xqi ruud erjqydut. Vkhjxuhcehu, jxuhu yi dem q isyudjyvys hqjyedqbu veh eriuhlydw fhefuh rkhyqb skijeci yd jxu Pedu, buij mu sxeeiu je vuut yji tqdwuhi ydijuqt.\ncc -2018"
 </text>
	</string>

	<!-- DRX Storyline Locked Case Quest Item -->
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_name">
		<text>Locked Case</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_2_desc">
		<text>A locked case. Not sure what's inside but it's heavy. Better be worth it lugging this thing around.</text>
	</string>

	<!-- DRX Storyline PDA Quest Item -->
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_sl_quest_item_3_desc">
		<text>An encrypted PDA. You have been promised a reward for its return.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psy-emissions. Needs adjusting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Uncalibrated psy-helmet</text>
	</string>

	<string id="good_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>Prototype developed by scientists to protect people from psy-emissions.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="good_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psy-helmet</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cit_doctors_key_short_desc">
		<text>Doctor's key to a secret stash in Pripyat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_name">
		<text>Doctor's key</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_key_desc">
		<text>A key with 'Hotel Polissya – Room 26' engraved on side.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_name">
		<text>Strelok's manuscript</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_docs_hiden_pri_desc">
		<text>Worn manuscript in leather binding. Written by Strelok himself.\nJudging by the headings alone, it might explain some of the Zone's secrets.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_name">
		<text>Doctor's notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cit_doctors_pda_desc">
		<text>'Just some notes about old men's conspiracy theories'.\n\nThere are rumours that the Agroprom Institute was used as a front for an unofficial lab in the years preceding the 2006 year accident. This lab hosted a number of very unusual experiments. The traders have dug up a lot of information about these laboratories. I met with the Barkeep, he says he sent Duty scouts to get into the underground vaults of the Dark Valley, called X-18, but they disappeared. There are another rumours regarding a 'psi-brain' mechanism. The whole neighbourhood in Yantar is under the influence of that piece of trash: it zombified everyone who came within range. There is another mechanism in the Red Forest radar underground, called lab X19, and that is what is likely to be the Brain Scorcher. There is evidence to suggest that the presence of the Brain Scorcher intentionally blocks the road to the North, but no one knows exactly what it is. The Barkeep believes that the Brain Scorcher is man-made, and these mechanisms are not always operating at full strength. He thinks there are periods when their power is lowered to cool down the apparatus. It's time to visit all the underground laboratories in the Zone and find out what kind of secrets they are hiding. Too bad, that I'm too old for this shit. I wish Strelok would be still around, but damn, he disappeared years ago.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_decoder_desc">
		<text>A powerful electronic lock-pick. Strangely enough, it does not seem to be an all-purpose thieves' instrument. Rather, it seems to have been created with a specific electronic lock in mind and can't be used to override anything else.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_decoder_name">
		<text>Decoder</text>
	</string>

	<string id="pri_decoder_docs_conclusion_txt">
		<text>The manuscript contains a short report on how Fang and Strelok infiltrated a hidden laboratory and their journey there. It makes mention of large Monolith presence in and around the Chernobyl NPP. More specifically under the concrete sarcophagus, also suggesting it may be their base of operations but with the intent to hide something. Reading further it states that they discovered laboratory hidden further in the north under the generators, however they were unable to gain access at the time of writing as they required the use of a decoder.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_quest_case_02_desc">
		<text>A fireproof briefcase containing military documents and reports on investigations performed near Agroprom. The reports talk in detail about how machinery and equipment has gone missing from the institute, and how the results of the investigations on their whereabouts were apparently falsified.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_quest_case_02_name">
		<text>Military documents</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x18_name">
		<text>Biology research report</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x18_desc">
		<text>The report details the study of biological samples sent from lab X-18. The samples were subjected to informational field effects of varying intensities. The report meticulously describes the mutation of living beings following exposure to emissions.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x16_desc">
		<text>The documents refer to one of the side discoveries of bio-research, specifically the discovery that living creatures are able to generate directed psy-emissions. A biological field emitter, essentially a giant brain, was grown as part of the research conducted in lab X16.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x16_name">
		<text>Psy research documents</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x10_desc">
		<text>The documents describe the technical characteristics of an antenna and how they deviate from their planned designs. There is a note on the reverse side which indicates that these documents were prepared in lab X19.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x10_name">
		<text>Rainbow emitter documents</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_x8_desc">
		<text>The document refers to the transfer of the research team and all materials to another laboratory far in the north, which will be used to research matters relating to the influence of the noosphere. To enter the lab, use the date of the accident as the code (ddmmyyyy).\n \nThe research team comprised: N.A. Lebedev, E.F. Kalancha and V.I. Suslov.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_x8_name">
		<text>Order of Transfer</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_desc">
		<text>The notebook contains a detailed description of an experiment assessing a psi-field's effect on an object in another hemisphere. A group of scientists in the Caribbean received the signal, but it was distorted. The signal was altered in a strange way, as though corrected by someone. A possible explanation is that the noosphere theory is correct and the changes were made by the noosphere.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_jup_ug_name">
		<text>Experiment notebook</text>
	</string>

	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name">
		<text>Prototype weapon report</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_doc_mon_con_name_desc">
		<text>Documents which describe the operating mechanism and main technical characteristics of a more advanced electromagnetic device.\nThere is a note inside the documents which reads: 'Documents must be returned to X8, the central laboratory. I will be busy, so deliver them yourself. — N. Lebedev'</text>
	</string>

	<string id="quest_package_name">
		<text>Package</text>
	</string>
	<string id="quest_package_desc">
		<text>The content of this package is unknown.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] personal belongings\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] valuable\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_jup_b32_scanner_device_name">
		<text>Anomalous Activity Scanner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jup_b32_scanner_device_desc">
		<text>This case combines an artefact detector, a battery and a powerful transmitter. The device will scan anomalies to determine the number and type of artefacts that appear. All of this information will be automatically relayed to the scientists' bunker.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_3]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[ui_gray_2] technological item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	

	<!-- MLR -->
	<string id="mlr_strelok_item_01">
		<text>Worn notebook</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mlr_strelok_item_01_desc">
		<text>A notebook, likely owned by Strelok himself. It describes in detail how to get into an underground complex called X-18.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="blackbox_mlr">
		<text>Flight recorder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="blackbox_mlr_descr">
		<text>A flight data recorder, or a "black box". Flight recorders are used to record the status of internal systems and crew conversations, and can provide vital information in the event of an accident. In the Zone, stalker and military personnel alike are interested in these devices.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="item_pda_map_mlr_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="item_pda_map_mlr_descr">
		<text>A PDA containing possible information on routes between different areas.</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<!-- DRX -->
	<string id="drx_x8_documents_name">
		<text>Antennas installation documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x8_documents_desc">
		<text>The document refers to what seems to be a massive radar installation. Most likely Brain Scorcher structure and operating system.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x16_documents_name">
		<text>Biological research</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x16_documents_desc">
		<text>A set of old papers that refer to experiments done on rats and other animals.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x18_documents_name">
		<text>Experiment report: B0-D4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x18_documents_desc">
		<text>Old documents that refer to an experiment related to psy-waves resonance and emitting.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_x19_documents_name">
		<text>Communication log / 21.03.2006</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_x19_documents_desc">
		<text>A printed transcription of the radio transmission between scientist groups from the institute.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_agr_u_documents_name">
		<text>Agroprom institute documentation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_agr_u_documents_desc">
		<text>A bunch of notes, pictures and a single marked map regarding Agroprom. Probably written by Strelok himself while being around.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="drx_jup_u_documents_name">
		<text>Transportation records</text>
	</string>
	<string id="drx_jup_u_documents_desc">
		<text>These documents refer to old records of transporting mechanical equipment and tools to the factory in Jupiter. It also includes geometric schemes for the tunnels toward the eastern side.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="lx8_history_documents_name">
		<text>Experimentation (11.04.2005)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_documents_desc">
		<text>This log documents the results of an experiment happened long years ago regarding new types of psy-emitters.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_2_documents_name">
		<text>Experimentation (24.09.2005)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_2_documents_desc">
		<text>This log documents the results of an experiment happened long years ago regarding psy-waves applications.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_3_documents_name">
		<text>Experimentation (02.05.2006)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="lx8_history_3_documents_desc">
		<text>This log documents the results of a biological experiment.</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
