<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>                                                                                                                              
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_1"><text>Haah... medkit... there we go. Not dead yet, not dead yet...</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_2"><text>DAMN! I'm going to need another tourniquet soon!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_3"><text>You're not the only one carrying meds, sucker.</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_4"><text>Uugh. So much blood. Bandages, bandages, bandages.... whew.</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_5"><text>Ghnaaa! Fuck, that's mine. That's my blood. No. Nononononono. Medkit, medkit-medkit! Aaah. Much better.</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_6"><text>I don't die so easily, fool!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_7"><text>You made me use my last medkit... I'm going to enjoy stripping your corpse.</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_8"><text>Come on, COME ON! I'm going to need another morphine shot!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_9"><text>Ah, hell. My kevlar's almost shredded!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_10"><text>Ngghhh. I'm going to give my medic a kiss if I survive this.</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_11"><text>I need more bandages over here!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_12"><text>GAH! Guess those looted meds were good for something after all...</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_13"><text>Mmmffffp! Insurance isn't going to cover this...</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_14"><text>Just need another shot, just need another shot, just need another shot...</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_15"><text>Guess that wasn't my last medkit, after all. I'm still in the fight, sucker!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_16"><text>Unnff. Bandage time. That might've killed me if you could aim worth a damn!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_17"><text>Inghh! Someone pass me another medkit! This one is finished!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_18"><text>A-aaaah-AAAAAAH! Mmmph. Thank God for morphine...</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_19"><text>It's going to take more than that to put me down, punk!</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_20"><text>AAARGH! Bloody, fu- EERRGHN! Medkit, medkit, medkit. Whew...</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_21"><text>You think you're going to bleed me out? Think again.</text></string>
	<string id="st_eat_medkit_cry_22"><text>Armour is still holding, armour is still holding, armour is still holding...</text></string>
</string_table>
